<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Upcoming FreeBSD Events</title>
    <link>http://www.FreeBSD.org/events/</link>
    <description>RSS feed of upcoming FreeBSD-related conferences, summits, courses, and other relevant events.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>freebsd-www@FreeBSD.org (FreeBSD Web Team)</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>freebsd-www@FreeBSD.org (FreeBSD Web Team)</managingEditor>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <ttl>120</ttl>
    <image>
      <url>http://www.FreeBSD.org/logo/logo-full.png</url>
      <title>Upcoming FreeBSD Events</title>
      <link>http://www.FreeBSD.org/events/</link>
    </image>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://www.FreeBSD.org/events/rss.xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Essen Hackathon 2018</title>
      <description>Essen Hackathon 2018 (https://wiki.freebsd.org/DevSummit/201808Hackathon), Linuxhotel Villa Vogelsang, Essen, Germany 2018 年 08 月 10 -  12 日. A weekend hackathon at the Linuxhotel in Essen,
      Germany. A great opportunity to fix bugs, commit code, tinker
      with devices, discuss new ideas, try out new things, and improve
      FreeBSD.</description>
      <link>https://wiki.freebsd.org/DevSummit/201808Hackathon</link>
      <guid>https://wiki.freebsd.org/DevSummit/201808Hackathon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EuroBSDcon 2018</title>
      <description>EuroBSDcon 2018 (https://2018.eurobsdcon.org), University Politehnica of Bucharest, Bucharest, Romania 2018 年 09 月 20 -  23 日. EuroBSDcon is the European annual technical
      conference gathering users and developers working on and with
      4.4BSD (Berkeley Software Distribution) based operating systems
      family and related projects. EuroBSDcon gives the exceptional
      opportunity to learn about latest news from the BSD world,
      witness contemporary deployment case studies, and meet
      personally other users and companies using BSD oriented
      technologies. EuroBSDcon is also a boiler plate for ideas,
      discussions and information exchange, which often turn into
      programming projects. The conference has always attracted active
      programmers, administrators and aspiring students, as well as IT
      companies at large, which found the conference a convenient and
      quality training option for its staff. We firmly believe that
      high profile education is vital to the future of technology, and
      hence greatly welcome students and young people to this regular
      meeting.</description>
      <link>https://2018.eurobsdcon.org</link>
      <guid>https://2018.eurobsdcon.org</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeetBSD 2018</title>
      <description>MeetBSD 2018 (https://www.meetbsd.com/), Intel Campus, Santa Clara, CA, United States 2018 年 10 月 19 -  20 日. MeetBSD 2018 is a mixed unConference format event
      featuring both scheduled talks and community-driven events such
      as birds-of-a-feather meetings and speed geeking
      sessions.</description>
      <link>https://www.meetbsd.com/</link>
      <guid>https://www.meetbsd.com/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
