<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>FreeBSD in the Press</title>
    <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html</link>
    <description>Press Stories about FreeBSD</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>freebsd-www@FreeBSD.org (Webmaster Team)</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>freebsd-www@FreeBSD.org (Webmaster Team)</managingEditor>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <ttl>120</ttl>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.FreeBSD.org/logo/logo-full.png</url>
      <title>FreeBSD in the Press</title>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html</link>
    </image>
    <atom:link href="https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press-rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Discussing Past, Present and Future of FreeBSD Project, itsfoss.com, Abhishek Prakash</title>
      <description>FreeBSD is one of the most popular BSD distributions. It is used on desktop, servers and embedded devices for more than two decades. We talked to Deb Goodkin, executive director, FreeBSD Foundation and discussed the past, present and future of FreeBSD project.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story202002:01</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story202002:01</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Feb 2020 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporting an open source operating system: a Q&amp;A
	  with the FreeBSD Foundation, techradar.com, </title>
      <description>When discussing alternative operating systems to Microsoft&#8217;s Windows or Apple&#8217;s macOS, Linux often comes to mind. However, while Linux is a recreation of UNIX, FreeBSD is more of a continuation. The free and open source operating system was initially developed by students at the University of California at Berkeley which is why the BSD in its name stands for Berkeley Software Distribution.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story202002:02</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story202002:02</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Feb 2020 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet FreeBSD Project &#8211; A Journey of 26 Years and
	  Beyond, pfind.com, William Chapman</title>
      <description>When talking about operating systems or platforms to run the whole computing processes for various devices, you might have heard about FreeBSD quite often. However, today&#8217;s implementations of this operating system are apparently not too well-known, and many people don&#8217;t know the contributions of FreeBSD in today&#8217;s computing technology. Since this operating system is not generally available for the average users, FreeBSD remains to be something that many people nowadays are not well-acquainted with. Yet, it has been used in various hardware and online platforms today, and it has been actively used for more than 26 years now.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201908:01</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201908:01</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Aug 2019 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD Turns 26, LWN.net, Sean Kerner</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD operating system is continuing to make progress, 26 years after it got its name. Among the areas where work is being done is on improved support for RISC-V, FUSE filesystem updates, C runtime changes, and security improvements. FreeBSD Day is celebrated on June 19, in recognition of the date in 1993 when the name FreeBSD was coined for a fork of the 386BSD project. The first official release of FreeBSD did not occur until November 1, 1993, however.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201906:01</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201906:01</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Jun 2019 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Popular Products You Didn't Know Were Built with Open
	  Source, DesignNews, Chris Wiltz</title>
      <description>A popular streaming service, video games consoles, and mobile messaging all owe a debt to FreeBSD.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201906:02</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201906:02</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Jun 2019 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD Foundation Announces FreeBSD Day on June 19,
	  2019, Brilliance Security Magazine, Editorial Staff</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD Foundation, supporters of FreeBSD, one of the oldest and largest open source computer operating systems in the world and used by many top corporations, has announced that June 19, 2019 is FreeBSD Day. FreeBSD Day marks the date in 1993 that developers named the new open source operating system and celebrates the impact FreeBSD has had on open source computing.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201906:03</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201906:03</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Jun 2019 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD ZFS vs. ZoL Performance, Ubuntu ZFS On Linux Reference, Phoronix, Michael Larabel</title>
      <description>Overall, the FreeBSD ZFS On Linux port is looking good so far and we are looking forward to it hopefully maturing in time for FreeBSD 13.0. Nice job to iX Systems and all of those involved, especially the ZFS On Linux project. Those wanting to help in testing can try the FreeBSD ZoL spins. Stay tuned for more benchmarks and on more diverse hardware as time allows and the FreeBSD ZoL support further matures, but so far at least the performance numbers are in good shape.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201904:01</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201904:01</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Apr 2019 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did we build our solution on top of FreeBSD?, Synergy SKY, Egil Hasting</title>
      <description>FreeBSD has given us the "it just works" experience, without sacrificing the full control. It feels and behaves mature and stable with great performance!</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201711:01</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201711:01</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Nov 2017 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD Project: Under the Hood, HostingAdvice.com, Alexandra Leslie</title>
      <description>With over 400 volunteer devs at its helm, the FreeBSD Project is a dynamic force that puts the control in administrators' hands. Project Committer Allan Jude has been a fan of the project since 2002. He discusses the system's internal structure and the feature functionality that drew him in &#8212; contributing to its documentation and then to its development &#8212; and what he's working on now, more than a decade later.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201606:01</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201606:01</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Jun 2016 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD now available in Azure Marketplace, Microsoft Azure Blog, Jason Anderson</title>
      <description>Microsoft excited to announce the availability of FreeBSD 10.3 as a ready-made VM image available directly from the Azure Marketplace. This means that not only can you quickly bring-up a FreeBSD VM in Azure, but also that in the event you need technical support, Microsoft support engineers can assist.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201606:02</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/news/press.html#story201606:02</guid>
      <pubDate>???, NaN Jun 2016 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
