<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>FreeBSD GNOME Project News</title>
    <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/</link>
    <description>FreeBSD GNOME News System</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>freebsd-gnome@FreeBSD.org (FreeBSD GNOME Team)</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>freebsd-gnome@FreeBSD.org (FreeBSD GNOME Team)</managingEditor>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <ttl>120</ttl>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.FreeBSD.org/logo/logo-full.png</url>
      <title>FreeBSD GNOME Project News</title>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/</link>
    </image>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/rss.xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 3.18 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD GNOME team proudly presents GNOME 3.18 for
	    FreeBSD.This update does not contain the glib and gtk c++ bindings
	    which will be done in a another update due to the requirement
	    on c++11 and the amount of fallout this probably will give.GDM is still at version 3.16 due to some issues.Bump mate-themes to use the gtk 3.18 version of the themes.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2016February14:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2016February14:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing MATE 1.12 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD GNOME team proudly presents MATE 1.12 for
	    FreeBSD.This version of MATE uses the GTK+ 2 toolkit for
	    stability, and has a number of bugfixes for the
	    applets.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2016January25:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2016January25:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 3.16.2 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD GNOME team proudly presents GNOME 3.16 for
	    FreeBSD.The official GNOME 3.16 release notes can be found at
	    https://help.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/3.16/.This release was made possible by these people:
	    Gustau Perez
	    
	    Ting-Wei_Lan
	    
	  </description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2015August5:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2015August5:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Aug 2015 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing MATE 1.10.0 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>Presenting the MATE 1.10.0 Desktop Environment for
	    FreeBSD.  The official release notes for this release can
	    be found at
	    https://mate-desktop.org/blog/2015-06-11-mate-1-10-released/This version of MATE is still built on the GTK+ 2
	    toolkit.Replace mate-dialogs with zenity and mate-calc with
	    galculator.Thanks go to Gustau Perez for helping track MATE
	    development.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2015July27:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2015July27:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 2.32.1 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>Presenting GNOME 2.32.1 for FreeBSD. The official release
	    notes for this release can be found at
	    http://library.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/2.32/This will be the last release of the GNOME 2.x series,
	    mainly a bugfix and bridge release to the first release of
	    the GNOME 3.x series.This release features commits by avl, marcus, mezz and
	    myself.The FreeBSD GNOME Team would like to thank the following
	    contributors and testers for there help with this
	    release:
	    Zane C.B.
	    
	    romain@
	    
	    Olaf Seibert
	    
	    DomiX
	    
	    Bapt
	    
	    jsa@
	    
	    miwi@
	    
	    Sergio de Almeida Lenzi
	    
	    Maxim Samsonov
	    
	    Kris Moore
	    </description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2010November19:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2010November19:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 2.30.1. for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>Presenting GNOME 2.30.1 for FreeBSD. The official release
	    notes for this release can be found at
	    http://library.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/2.30/This release brings initial PackageKit support, Upower
	    (replaces power management part of hal), cuse4bsd
	    integration with HAL and cheese, and a faster
	    Evolution.Sadly GNOME 2.30.x will be the last release with FreeBSD
	    6.X support.  This will also be the last of the 2.x
	    releases.  The next release will be the highly-anticipated
	    GNOME 3.0 which will bring with it a new UI
	    experience.Currently, there are a few bugs with GNOME 2.30 that may
	    be of note for our users.  Be sure to consult the 2.30
	    upgrade FAQ at
	    https://www.freebsd.org/gnome/docs/faq230.html
	    for specific upgrading instructions, and the up-to-date
	    list of known issues.This release features commits by: avl, ahze, bland,
	    marcus, mezz and myself.The FreeBSD GNOME Team would like to thank Anders F
	    Bjorklund for doing the initial packagekit porting.And the following contributors and testers for there help
	    with this release:
	    Eric L. Chen
	    

	    Vladimir Grebenschikov
	    

	    Sergio de Almeida Lenzi
	    

	    DomiX
	    

	    walder
	    

	    crsd
	    

	    Kevin Oberman
	    

	    Michal Varga
	    

	    Pavel Plesov
	    

	    Bapt
	    

	    kevin
	    

	    and Ion-Mihai Tetcu for running two exp-runs for us.
	    </description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2010May10:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2010May10:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 2.28.1. for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>Presenting GNOME 2.28.1 for FreeBSD. The official release
	    notes for this release can be found at
	    http://library.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/2.28/.
	    Officially, this is mostly a polishing release in
	    preparation for GNOME 3.0 due in about a year.On the FreeBSD front, though, a lot went into this
	    release.  Major thanks goes to kwm and avl who did a lot
	    of the porting work for this release.  In particular, kwm
	    brought in Evolution MAPI support for better Microsoft
	    Exchange integration.  Avl made sure that the new gobject
	    introspection repository ports were nicely
	    compartmentalized so that large dependencies aren't
	    brought in wholesale.But, every GNOME team member (ahze, avl, bland, kwm,
	    mezz, and myself) contributed to this release.Other major improvements include an updated HAL with
	    better volume probing code, ufsid integration, and support
	    for volume names containing spaces (big thanks to J.R.
	    Oldroyd); a new WebKit; updated AbiWord; an updated Gimp;
	    and a preview of the new GNOME Shell project (thanks to
	    Pawel Worach).The FreeBSD GNOME Team would like to that the following
	    additional contributors to this release whose patches and
	    testing really helped make it a success:
	    Andrius Morkunas
	    

	    Dominique Goncalves
	    

	    Eric L. Chen
	    

	    J.R. Oldroyd
	    

	    Joseph S. Atkinson
	    

	    Li
	    

	    Pawel Worach
	    

	    Romain Tarti?re
	    

	    Thomas Vogt
	    

	    Yasuda Keisuke
	    

	    Rui Paulo
	    

	    Martin Wilke
	    

	    (and an extra shout out to miwi and pav for the pointyhat
	    runs) We would like to send this release out to Alexander
	    Loginov (avl) in hopes that he feels better soon.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2009November28:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2009November28:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 2.26.0 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD GNOME team is proud to announce the release
	    of GNOME 2.26.0 for FreeBSD. The official release notes
	    can be found at
	    http://library.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/2.26/.

	    On the FreeBSD front, we introduced a port of libxul 1.9
	    as an alternative for Firefox 2.0 as a Gecko provider.
	    Almost all of the Gecko consumers can make use of this
	    provider by setting:
	    

	    WITH_GECKO=libxul
	    

	    The GNOME 2.26 port was done by ahze, kwm, marcus, and
	    mezz with contributions by Joseph S. Atkinson, Peter Wemm,
	    Eric L. Chen, Martin Matuska, Craig Butler, and Pawel
	    Worach.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2009April10:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2009April10:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2009 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 2.24.2 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD GNOME team is proud to announce the release
	    of GNOME 2.24.2 for FreeBSD. The official release notes
	    can be found at
	    http://library.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/2.24/.

	    On the FreeBSD front, this release introduces Fuse support
	    in HAL, adds multi-CPU support to libgtop, WebKit updates,
	    and fixes some long-standing seahorse and gnome-keyring
	    bugs.This release features commits by adamw, ahze, kwm, mezz,
	    and myself.  It would not have been possible without are
	    contributors and testers: Alexander Loginov, Craig Butler,
	    Dmitry Marakasov, Eric L. Chen, Joseph S. Atkinson, Kris
	    Moore, Lapo Luchini, Nikos Ntarmos, Pawel Worach, Romain
	    Tartiere, TAOKA Fumiyoshi, Romain Tartiere, Yasuda
	    Keisuke, Zyl aZ, bf, Florent Thoumie, Peter Wemm, and
	    pluknet.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2009January9:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2009January9:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 9 Jan 2009 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GNOME 2.22.0 for FreeBSD!</title>
      <description>The FreeBSD GNOME team is proud to announce the release
	    of GNOME 2.22.0 for FreeBSD. The official GNOME 2.22
	    release notes can be found at
	    http://library.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/2.22/.

	    On the FreeBSD front, this release features an updated hal
	    port with support for video4linux devices, DRM (Direct
	    Rendering), and better support of removable media.  Work
	    is also underway to tie webkit more closely into GNOME. As
	    part of the GNOME 2.22 upgrade, GStreamer received a
	    rather large upgrade as well.  Be sure to consult UPDATING
	    on the proper steps to upgrade all of your GNOME
	    ports.This release would not have been possible without the
	    contributions and testing efforts of the following people:
	    Pawel Worach, kan, edwin, Peter Ulrich Kruppa, J. W.
	    Ballantine, Yasuda Keisuke, and Andriy Gapon.</description>
      <link>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2008March24:0</link>
      <guid>https://www.FreeBSD.org/gnome/newsflash.html#event2008March24:0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
